

Henrik Mjaaland

Computer Engineer

(1)

18 November 1993



Gamleveien 14, 4315 Sandnes, Rogaland



+47 90215974



http://github.com/henmja



henrikmjaaland@hotmail.com

About Me ———

I am a computer engineer from Sandnes, Norway. I live in Lura with my fiancée. I have a bachelor degree in Computer Science, and I am currently working on a masters degree (also Computer Science). I have previously worked as a production operator, seller, gardener, and as a warehouse worker. Preesently, I am working as a control technician for Nærbø Kyllingslakt. There, the tasks are IT-related (f.ex. control the assembly lines). In my sparetime I like to run, lift, bike and play football. As a person I am outgoing, hard-working and honest.

MAILAL

Go

Javascript

PHP

(*)[The skill scale is from 0 (Fundamental Awareness) to 6 (Expert).]

Education

since 2017	M.Sc.	University of Stavanger
	Computer Science	

University of Stavanger

Sandnes VGS

2014-2016 B.Sc. Computer Science

2009-2012 General Studies

Science

Portfolio

Github.com/Henmja

Website

https://www.henrikmjaaland.com

Certificates

2012	Driver's License, Class B
2012	Forklift License, T1
2016	Boating License

Experience

Nærbø Kyllingslakt	Control Technician	Current
Nortura Forus	Production Operator	2017-18
Facility Services	Gardener	2016
Megaflis Forus	Warehouse Worker	2015
Burger Pizza Companiet	Seller	2013-14
REMA 1000 Distribusjon	Warehouse Worker	2012

References

References are given on demand.